A Guide to the Barbara Whaley Bitters Hall Papers, 1975-1997
Library of Virginia
- AT & T CONSUMER ADVISORY PANEL
  - Reports, JTP (Joint Telecommunications Project), Disabled consumers, 1987 (Box-folder Box 18 Folder 2)
  - Reports, JTP, National survey, 1987 (Box-folder Box 18 Folder 3)
  - Reports, JTP, Project summary, 1987 (Box-folder Box 18 Folder 4)
  - Reports, JTP, Survey of Households Without Telephones- California, 1987 (Box-folder Box 18 Folder 5)
  - Reports, JTP, Surveys of Households Without Telephones- Florida, 1987 (Box-folder Box 18 Folder 6)
  - Reports, JTP, Surveys of Households Without Telephones- Texas, 1987 (Box-folder Box 18 Folder 7)
  - Reports, JTP, Telecommunications and healthcare- California, 1987 (Box-folder Box 19 Folder 1)
  - Reports, JTP, Telecommunications and healthcare- Florida, 1987 (Box-folder Box 19 Folder 2)
  - Reports, JTP, Telecommunications and healthcare- New York, 1987 (Box-folder Box 19 Folder 3)
  - Reports, JTP, Telecommunications and healthcare- Texas, 1987 (Box-folder Box 19 Folder 4)
  - Reports, Miscellaneous, 1986-1987 (Box-folder Box 19 Folder 5)
  - Reports, Miscellaneous, 1988-1989 (Box-folder Box 19 Folder 6)
  - Reports, Miscellaneous, 1990-1992 (Box-folder Box 20 Folder 1)
  - Reports, Miscellaneous, 1993-1994 (Box-folder Box 20 Folder 2)
  - Reports, Miscellaneous, nd (Box-folder Box 20 Folder 3)
  - Reports, Telecommunication Needs of Older, Lower Income Consumers, 1987 (Box-folder Box 20 Folder 4)
  - Reports, Telecommunications Policy Regarding Deregulation, 1988 (Box-folder Box 20 Folder 5)
  - Speeches, AT & T, Allen, Robert E. 1989-1997 (Box-folder Box 20 Folder 6)
  - Speeches, AT & T, Miscellaneous, 1990-1997 (Box-folder Box 20 Folder 7)
  - Speeches, Miscellaneous, 1987-1993 (Box-folder Box 20 Folder 8)
  - Speeches, Miscellaneous, 1994-1995 (Box-folder Box 21 Folder 1)
  - Tele-Consumer Hotline, Information package, 1988-1989 (Box-folder Box 21 Folder 2)
  - Tele-Consumer Hotline, Statistical reports, 1988 (Box-folder Box 21 Folder 3)
  - Tele-Consumer Hotline, Statistical reports, 1989 (Box-folder Box 21 Folder 4)
  - U.S. vs. Western Electric Co., AT & T comments, 1987 (Box-folder Box 21 Folder 5)
  - U.S. vs. Western Electric Co., Opinions and orders, 1988 (Box-folder Box 21 Folder 6)
- Series II: C &P TELEPHONE: VIRGINIA CONSUMER COUNCIL
  This series is arranged alphabetically in 5 archival boxes and contains advertisements, clippings, correspondence, guidelines and procedures, legal materials, membership lists, memoranda, minutes, newsletters, publications, press releases, reports, and surveys. The Consumer Council board was formed to develop and recommend policy changes to the Chesapeake and Potomac Telephone Company and consisted of members from business, consumer groups, senior citizens, disabled and grassroots groups. Hall served on the committee from 1982-1992. Issues addressed by the Council include deregulation of the telephone industry, rate increases, telemarketing fraud, and services for the disabled. Included are acts regarding telephone solicitation and pay per call services before the Virginia General Assembly, and comments by the Virginia State Corporation Commission concerning the AT&T and Department of Justice consent decree. Also included are minutes, reports, and surveys of the Lifeline Telephone Service Committee, a committee formed to study providing low-cost telephone services and low connection fees for the elderly and poor in Virginia. The series also contains information on a variety of C&P telephone services, including caller id, extended local area calling, and operator assistance. Also includes the C&P newsletters, "Fast Facts," "C&P Scene," and "Bell Atlantic Times."
  - Advertising, 1985 (Box-folder Box 22 Folder 1)
  - Annual report, 1985-1988 (Box-folder Box 22 Folder 2)
  - Biographies, nd (Box-folder Box 22 Folder 3)
  - Blue pages, 1992 (Box-folder Box 22 Folder 4)
  - Board orientation handbook, Section 1, c. 1981 (Box-folder Box 22 Folder 5)
  - Board orientation handbook, Section 2, c. 1981 (Box-folder Box 22 Folder 6)
  - Cllippings, 1982-1989 (Box-folder Box 22 Folder 7)
  - Clippings, 1990 (Box-folder Box 22 Folder 8)
  - Clippings, 1990, January- July (Box-folder Box 22 Folder 9)
  - Clippings, 1991, August-1995 (Box-folder Box 23 Folder 1)
  - Clippings, nd (Box-folder Box 23 Folder 2)
  - Conferences, Telephone issues, 1986-1987 (Box-folder Box 23 Folder 3)
  - Conferences, WAVE, 1992 (Box-folder Box 23 Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1979-1985 (Box-folder Box 23 Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box-folder Box 23 Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box-folder Box 23 Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box-folder Box 23 Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box-folder Box 23 Folder 9)
  - Greenwood Partnership, 1990 (Box-folder Box 23 Folder 10)
  - Guidelines and procedures, 1984-1991 (Box-folder Box 23 Folder 11)
  - Legislation, miscellaneous 1985-1989 (Box-folder Box 24 Folder 1)
  - Lifeline Telephone Service Committee, Minutes, 1985-1987 (Box-folder Box 24 Folder 2)
  - Lifeline Telephone Service Committee, Reports, 1985-1987 (Box-folder Box 24 Folder 3)
  - Lifeline Telephone Service Committee, Study, 1987 (Box-folder Box 24 Folder 4)
  - Lifeline Telephone Service Committee, Survey, 1985 (Box-folder Box 24 Folder 5)
  - Membership directory, 1982-1992 (Box-folder Box 24 Folder 6)
  - Memoranda 1985-1993 (Box-folder Box 24 Folder 7)
  - Minutes, 1982-1986 (Box-folder Box 24 Folder 8)
  - Minutes, 1987 (Box-folder Box 24 Folder 9)
  - Minutes, 1988 (Box-folder Box 24 Folder 10)
  - Minutes, 1989-1990 (Box-folder Box 25 Folder 1)
  - Minutes, 1991-1992 (Box-folder Box 25 Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous, 1985-1987 (Box-folder Box 25 Folder 3)
  - Newsletters, C & P, 1982-1992 (Box-folder Box 25 Folder 4)
  - Newsletters, Miscellaneous, 1981-1991 (Box-folder Box 25 Folder 5)
  - Press releases, C & P, 1982-1992 (Box-folder Box 25 Folder 6)
  - Press releases, Miscellaneous, 1982-1991 (Box-folder Box 25 Folder 7)
  - Publications, C & P, 1985-1988 (Box-folder Box 25 Folder 8)
  - Publications, Miscellaneous, 1987-1988 (Box-folder Box 25 Folder 9)
  - Reports, Caller ID Service, 1988 (Box-folder Box 25 Folder 10)
  - Reports, Code exhaust, 1987 (Box-folder Box 26 Folder 1)
  - Reports, Divestiture plus eight, 1991 (Box-folder Box 26 Folder 2)
  - Reports, EAC/LMS Trial, c. 1981 (Box-folder Box 26 Folder 3)
  - Reports, Miscellaneous, 1982-1986 (Box-folder Box 26 Folder 4)
  - Reports, Miscellaneous, 1987-1991 (Box-folder Box 26 Folder 5)
  - Speeches, 1986-1991 (Box-folder Box 26 Folder 6)
  - Subisdiaries flow chart nd (Box-folder Box 26 Folder 7)
  - Surveys, 1988 (Box-folder Box 26 Folder 8)
  - Telephone services, c. 1982-1992 (Box-folder Box 26 Folder 9)
  - Virginia General Assembly 1991-1993 (Box-folder Box 26 Folder 10)
  - Virginia State Corporation Commission 1982-1988 (Box-folder Box 26 Folder 11)
- SERIES III: CONFERENCE OF CONSUMER ORGANIZATIONS (COCO)
  This series is arranged alphabetically in 4 boxes and contains clippings, correspondence, conference materials, leaflets, minutes, newsletters, publications, reports and speeches. COCO was established in 1973, as a spin-off of the Consumer Federation of America, to improve communication and cooperation in the consumer actions programs throughout the country. The organization assisted local and state consumer groups, provided consumer education, and sponsored numerous consumer-industry panels and roundtables. Starting in 1975 COCO began an association with AT&T which led to, in the late 1980's, the creation of the AT&T Consumer Advisory Panel. Barbara Hall was a member and secretary of COCO from 1976-1997. Of note within the series are the programs, pamphlets, and lists of participants of the numerous conferences sponsored by COCO, including the COCO National Conference held in Richmond, Virginia in 1985. The series also contains copies of COCO's newsletter, "Intercom," 1978-1996.
  - Clippings, 1975-1977 (Box-folder Box 27 Folder 1)
  - Conferences: CFA: Consumer Assembly, 1993 (Box-folder Box 27 Folder 2)
  - Conferences: CFA: Consumer Assembly, 1994 (Box-folder Box 27 Folder 3)
  - Conferences: CFA: Consumer Assembly, 1995 (Box-folder Box 27 Folder 4)
  - Conferences: CFA: Consumer Assembly, 1996 (Box-folder Box 27 Folder 5)
  - Conferences: CFA: Consumers and Utilites, 1995 (Box-folder Box 27 Folder 6)
  - Conferences: CFA: Consumers and Utilities, 1996 (Box-folder Box 27 Folder 7)
  - Conferences: Eastern Consumer Conferences, 1978-1981 (Box-folder Box 27 Folder 8)
  - Conferences: Eastern Consumer Conferences, 1982-1985 (Box-folder Box 27 Folder 9)
  - Conferences: Miscellaneous 1979-1986 (Box-folder Box 27 Folder 10)
  - Conferences: Public Voices's, 1994 (Box-folder Box 27 Folder 11)
  - Conferences: Public Voice's, 1996 (Box-folder Box 28 Folder 1)
  - Conferences: Public Voice's, 1997 (Box-folder Box 28 Folder 2)
  - Conferences: Public Voice's, 1997 (Box-folder Box 28 Folder 3)
  - CFA: Food and nutrition subcommittee, 1996 (Box-folder Box 28 Folder 4)
  - Correspondence 1979-1985 (Box-folder Box 28 Folder 5)
  - Institute for Community Services, 1982 (Box-folder Box 28 Folder 6)
  - Membership directory, nd (Box-folder Box 28 Folder 7)
  - Memoranda, 1979-1986 (Box-folder Box 28 Folder 8)
  - Minutes, 1979-1993 (Box-folder Box 28 Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous, 1978-1990 (Box-folder Box 28 Folder 10)
  - Newsletters, Intercom, 1978-1988 (Box-folder Box 29 Folder 1)
  - Newsletters, Intercom, 1989-1992 (Box-folder Box 29 Folder 2)
  - Newsletters, Intercom, 1993-1997 (Box-folder Box 29 Folder 3)
  - Newsletters, Miscellaneous, 1982-1990 (Box-folder Box 29 Folder 4)
  - Publications, 1982-1990 (Box-folder Box 29 Folder 5)
  - Reports: Expanding the information age, 1990 (Box-folder Box 30 Folder 1)
  - Reports: Harvesting our choices, 1984 (Box-folder Box 30 Folder 2)
  - Reports: Pennsylania Power and Light Company, 1980 (Box-folder Box 30 Folder 3)
  - Reports: Professional, occupational, and institutional licensing, 1978 (Box-folder Box 30 Folder 4)
  - Reports: Restructuring of the electric utility industry, 1997 (Box-folder Box 30 Folder 5)
  - Speeches, 1979-1982 (Box-folder Box 30 Folder 6)
- Series IV: GENERAL
  This series is arranged alphabetically in 13 boxes and contains annual reports, bylaws, clippings, correspondence, newsletters, minutes, pamphlets, membership directories, legislative bills, reports, publications, memoranda, and speeches. This series contains information on a variety of organizations and subjects including, Alternative Medicine, Consumer Education & Information Association of Virginia (CEIAV), Farmers Market (Richmond, Va.), Fluoride, Occupational licensing, Virginia Cooperative Extension (VCE), Virginia Pharmaceutical Association (VPhA), and the Women's Bank (Richmond, Va.). Included in the VCE section is information on the Virginia Agricultural Sustainability Leadership Council (VASLC) and the Family and Consumer Science Leadership Council (FCS). Hall served on the board, lobbied and was a co- founder of many of the organizations.
  - Alternative medicine, FAIM, 1997 (Box-folder Box 31 Folder 1)
  - Alternative medicine, Miscellaneous, 1978-1997 (Box-folder Box 31 Folder 2)
  - Alternative medicinie, Virginia Board of Health Professions, Miscellaneous, 1996-1997 (Box-folder Box 31 Folder 3)
  - Alternative medicinie, Virginia Board of Health Processions, Report, Background, 1997 (Box-folder Box 31 Folder 4)
  - Alternative medicine, Virginia Board of Health Professions, Report, Supplement, 1997 (Box-folder Box 31 Folder 5)
  - Alternative medicinie, Virginia Board of Health Professions, Report, Appendix A, 1997 (Box-folder Box 31 Folder 6)
  - Alternative medicine, Virginia Alliance for Health Care Freedom, 1993-1995 (Box-folder Box 31 Folder 7)
  - Alternative medicine, Virginia Alliance for Health Care Freedom, 1997 (Box-folder Box 31 Folder 8)
  - Alternative medicinie, Virginia Alliance for Health Care Freedom, 1997 (Box-folder Box 32 Folder 1)
  - Citizens on Board, 1982 (Box-folder Box 32 Folder 2)
  - Consumer Education and Information Association of Virginia (CEIAV) 1978 (Box-folder Box 32 Folder 3)
  - CEIAV, 1979 (Box-folder Box 32 Folder 4)
  - CEIAV, 1980-1981 (Box-folder Box 32 Folder 5)
  - CEIAV, 1982-1983 (Box-folder Box 32 Folder 6)
  - CEIAV, 1984-1985 (Box-folder Box 32 Folder 7)
  - CEIAV, 1986-1987 (Box-folder Box 33 Folder 1)
  - CEIAV, 1988 (Box-folder Box 33 Folder 2)
  - CEIAV, 1989-1996 (Box-folder Box 33 Folder 3)
  - Council of State Governments 1981 (Box-folder Box 33 Folder 4)
  - Farmer's Market (Richmond, Virginia) 1978-1981 (Box-folder Box 33 Folder 5)
  - Farmer's Market 1994 (Box-folder Box 33 Folder 6)
  - Farmer's Market, 1995 (Box-folder Box 33 Folder 7)
  - Farmer's Market, Business plan, 1995 (Box-folder Box 33 Folder 8)
  - Farmer's Market, 1996 (Box-folder Box 34 Folder 1)
  - Farmer's Market, Business plan 1996 (Box-folder Box 34 Folder 2)
  - Farmer's Market, Business plan, 1996 (Box-folder Box 34 Folder 3)
  - Farmer's Market, 1997, February-June (Box-folder Box 34 Folder 4)
  - Farmer's Market, 1997, July-December (Box-folder Box 34 Folder 5)
  - Farmer's Market, Business plan, 1997 (Box-folder Box 34 Folder 6)
  - Farmer's Market, nd (Box-folder Box 34 Folder 7)
  - Flouride, 1977-1981 (Box-folder Box 35 Folder 1)
  - Flouride, 1982 (Box-folder Box 35 Folder 2)
  - Flouride, 1983-1984 (Box-folder Box 35 Folder 3)
  - Flouride, 1987-1995 (Box-folder Box 35 Folder 4)
  - Hookups Inc., 1996 (Box-folder Box 35 Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous, 1977 (Box-folder Box 35 Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous, 1978 (Box-folder Box 35 Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous, 1979, January-February (Box-folder Box 36 Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous, 1979, March (Box-folder Box 36 Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous, 1979, April (Box-folder Box 36 Folder 3)
  - Miscelleous, 1979, May (Box-folder Box 36 Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous, 1979, June-August (Box-folder Box 36 Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous, 1979, September-December (Box-folder Box 36 Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous, 1980 (Box-folder Box 36 Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous, Legis/50, 1980 (Box-folder Box 37 Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous, 1981 (Box-folder Box 37 Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous, 1981 (Box-folder Box 37 Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous, 1981 (Box-folder Box 37 Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous, 1981 (Box-folder Box 37 Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous, 1982 (Box-folder Box 37 Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous, 1982 (Box-folder Box 38 Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous, 1982 (Box-folder Box 38 Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous, 1983-1984 (Box-folder Box 38 Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous, 1985 (Box-folder Box 38 Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous, 1986 (Box-folder Box 38 Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous, 1987 (Box-folder Box 38 Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous, 1988 (Box-folder Box 38 Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous, 1991-1992 (Box-folder Box 39 Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous, 1993-1994 (Box-folder Box 39 Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous, 1995 (Box-folder Box 39 Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous, 1996-1997 (Box-folder Box 39 Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous, nd (Box-folder Box 39 Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous, nd (Box-folder Box 39 Folder 6)
  - Occupational licensing, 1980 (Box-folder Box 39 Folder 7)
  - Occupational licensing, Report, 1980 (Box-folder Box 40 Folder 1)
  - Occupational licensing, 1981 (Box-folder Box 40 Folder 2)
  - Occupational licensing, 1982 (Box-folder Box 40 Folder 3)
  - Privacy Journal, 1991-1992 (Box-folder Box 40 Folder 4)
  - Privacy Journal, 1993-1994 (Box-folder Box 40 Folder 5)
  - Privacy Journal, 1995-1997 (Box-folder Box 40 Folder 6)
  - VCE: Family and Consumer Science Leadership Council, 1988-1995 (Box-folder Box 41 Folder 1)
  - VCE: Family and Consumer Science Leadership Council, 1996, January-July (Box-folder Box 41 Folder 2)
  - VCE: Family and Consumer Science Leadership Council, 1996, August-December (Box-folder Box 41 Folder 3)
  - VCE: Family and Consumer Science Leadership Council, 1997 (Box-folder Box 41 Folder 4)
  - VCE: Family and Consumer Science Leadership Council, nd (Box-folder Box 41 Folder 5)
  - VCE: Virginia Agricultural Sustainability Leadership Council, 1994-1997 (Box-folder Box 42 Folder 1)
  - VCE: Virginia Agricultural Sustainability Leadership Council, Manual, 1997 (Box-folder Box 42 Folder 2)
  - Virginia Pharmaceutical Association, 1979-1980 (Box-folder Box 42 Folder 3)
  - Virginia Pharmaceutical Association, 1981 (Box-folder Box 42 Folder 4)
  - Virginia Pharmaceutical Association, 1981 (Box-folder Box 42 Folder 5)
  - Virginia Pharmaceutical Association, 1982 (Box-folder Box 42 Folder 6)
  - Virginia Pharmaceutical Association, 1983-1988 (Box-folder Box 42 Folder 7)
  - Virginia Pharmaceutical Association, 1989-1996 (Box-folder Box 43 Folder 1)
  - Women's Bank (Richmond, Va.) 1976-1977 (Box-folder Box 43 Folder 2)
  - Women's Bank (Richmond, Va.) 1978-1979 (Box-folder Box 43 Folder 3)
  - Women's Bank (Richmond, Va.) 1980 (Box-folder Box 43 Folder 4)
  - Women's Bank (Richmond, Va.) 1981 (Box-folder Box 43 Folder 5)
  - Women's Bank (Richmond, Va.) 1982 (Box-folder Box 43 Folder 6)
  - Women's Bank (Richmond, Va.) 1983 (Box-folder Box 43 Folder 7)
- Series V: U.S. CONSUMER PRODUCT SAFETY COMMISSION (USCPSC)
  This series is arranged alphabetically in 3 boxes and contains annual reports, clippings, correspondence, membership lists, memoranda, newsletters, press releases, publications, and reports. Hall served on the Product Safety Advisory Council of the USCPSC from 1979-1981. The USCPSC was organized in 1972 by Congress to protect and inform consumers on the hazards associated with consumer products, assist customers in evaluating the safety of consumer products, develop uniform safety standards, and promote research and investigations. The collection contains information regarding the safety advisories, recalls, and repairs issued by the USCPSC during Hall's association. The commission addressed issues relating to burn and poison prevention, toy and household product safety. The collection contains a number of fact sheets and publications relating to household safety with bicycles, lawn mowers, Christmas lights, skateboards, and skis. Also included are classroom activity workbooks on poison prevention and toy safety, and an issue of "Sprocket Man," a comic book which addressed bicycle safety. Also includes opinions and speeches given by members of the USCPSC, a report issued by the Carter Administration on regulatory reform, staff briefing packages, report on the Recall Effectiveness Task Force, and agendas and minutes from the Product Safety Advisory Council.
  - Annual reports 1978-1980 (Box-folder Box 44 Folder 1)
  - Clippings, 1979-1980 (Box-folder Box 44 Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1979-1981 (Box-folder Box 44 Folder 3)
  - Dissenting opinions, 1979-1980 (Box-folder Box 44 Folder 4)
  - Memoranda, 1979 (Box-folder Box 44 Folder 5)
  - Memoranda, 1980-1981 (Box-folder Box 45 Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous, 1979-1981 (Box-folder Box 45 Folder 2)
  - Newsletters, 1978-1980 (Box-folder Box 45 Folder 3)
  - Press releases, 1979-1981 (Box-folder Box 45 Folder 4)
  - Product safety advisory council, Agendas, 1979-1981 (Box-folder Box 45 Folder 5)
  - Product safety advisory council, Members, 1979-1981 (Box-folder Box 45 Folder 6)
  - Product safety advisory council, Miscellaneous, 1979-1981 (Box-folder Box 45 Folder 7)
  - Publications, Consumer Resource Handbook, 1979 (Box-folder Box 45 Folder 8)
  - Publications, Journal National Cancer Institute, 1979 (Box-folder Box 45 Folder 9)
  - Publications, Product safety, 1979-1981 (Box-folder Box 45 Folder 10)
  - Recall effectiveness task force, 1980 (Box-folder Box 46 Folder 1)
  - Reports, Miscellaneous, 1978-1979 (Box-folder Box 46 Folder 2)
  - Reports, The President's Program, 1979 (Box-folder Box 46 Folder 3)
  - Reports, Statutory Rule Review, 1980 (Box-folder Box 46 Folder 4)
  - Reports, Voluntary Standards, 1979 (Box-folder Box 46 Folder 5)
  - Speeches, 197-1981 (Box-folder Box 46 Folder 6)
  - Staff briefing packages, 1980 (Box-folder Box 46 Folder 7)
- Series VI: VIRGINIA ASSOCIATION FOR BIOLOGICAL FARMERS (VABF)
  This series is arranged alphabetically in 5 boxes and includes clippings, correspondence, minutes, newsletters, publications, and reports. The V.A.B.F. was an organization founded in 1977 to provide information and services to farmers, gardeners, and consumers about biological agriculture in Virginia. The series contains copies of the by-laws, directories of biological farmers, shippers, grocers, and restaurants in Virginia, and minutes, agendas, and financial statements of the organization. The publications include brochures, catalogs, and pamphlets on a wide range of subjects, from the proper way to cure hams Virginia style, to nutrition guidebooks. The series also contains copies of the V.A.B.F. newsletter from 1984-1997, and other miscellaneous newsletters such as, "The Rural Virginia" and "Southern Sustainable Farming."
  - Advertisements, 1996 (Box-folder Box 47 Folder 1)
  - Biological production, 1996 (Box-folder Box 47 Folder 2)
  - Buy-Green Virginia, 1997 (Box-folder Box 47 Folder 3)
  - By-laws, nd (Box-folder Box 47 Folder 4)
  - Clippings, 1977-1997 (Box-folder Box 47 Folder 5)
  - Conferences, Miscellaneous, 1994-1997 (Box-folder Box 47 Folder 6)
  - Conferences, Southern sustainable agriculture, 1996 (Box-folder Box 47 Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1985-1995 (Box-folder Box 47 Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box-folder Box 47 Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, nd (Box-folder Box 47 Folder 10)
  - Farmer's Market (Richmond, Va.), 1996 (Box-folder Box 47 Folder 11)
  - Food Alternatives with Relationship Marketing (FARM), 1996-1997 (Box-folder Box 47 Folder 12)
  - Marketing Committee,, 1990-1994 (Box-folder Box 48 Folder 1)
  - Marketing Committee, nd (Box-folder Box 48 Folder 2)
  - Membership directory, 1994-1996 (Box-folder Box 48 Folder 3)
  - Minutes, 1994-1997 (Box-folder Box 48 Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous, 1990-1997 (Box-folder Box 48 Folder 5)
  - Newsletters, Miscellaneous, 1995-1997 (Box-folder Box 48 Folder 6)
  - Newsletters, The Rural Virginia, 1985-1988 (Box-folder Box 48 Folder 7)
  - Newsletters, The Virginia Biological Farmer, 1984-1990 (Box-folder Box 48 Folder 8)
  - Newsletters, The Virginia Biological Farmer, 1991-1993 (Box-folder Box 48 Folder 9)
  - Newsletters, The Virginia Biological Farmer, 1994 (Box-folder Box 49 Folder 1)
  - Newsletters, The Virginia Biological Farmer, 1995 (Box-folder Box 49 Folder 2)
  - Newsletters, The Virginia Biological Farmer, 1996-1997 (Box-folder Box 49 Folder 3)
  - Notes, nd (Box-folder Box 49 Folder 4)
  - Press contacts, nd (Box-folder Box 49 Folder 5)
  - Publications, Beef-Spading machines, 1977-1985 (Box-folder Box 49 Folder 6)
  - Publications, Leaflets, 1993-1997 (Box-folder Box 49 Folder 7)
  - Publicatioins, Miscellaneous, 1995-1997 (Box-folder Box 49 Folder 8)
  - Publications, Virginia agricultural organizations, 1982-1994 (Box-folder Box 49 Folder 9)
  - Reports, Agricultural law: Virginia law, 1984 (Box-folder Box 49 Folder 10)
  - Reports, Are functional foods the solution to dysfunctional diets?, 1997 (Box-folder Box 49 Folder 11)
  - Reports, Environmentally-sustaining agriculture, 1997 (Box-folder Box 49 Folder 12)
  - Reports, Harvesting our choices: Virginia food system, 1984 (Box-folder Box 49 Folder 13)
  - Reports, Highlights on surveys of interest and use of farm based computers, 1986 (Box-folder Box 49 Folder 14)
  - Reports, Miscellaneous, 1993-1997 (Box-folder Box 50 Folder 1)
  - Reports, Mulching practices, 1995 (Box-folder Box 50 Folder 2)
  - Reports, The need for a research-intensive nutraceutical industry, 1996 (Box-folder Box 50 Folder 3)
  - Reports, New partnerships for sustainable agriculture, 1996 (Box-folder Box 50 Folder 4)